A Finding Aid to the Everett Shinn Collection, 1877-1958, in the Archives of American Art AAA.shinever
Archives of American Art
- Photographs, 1877-1950; Series 8; 1.3 Linear feet Box 2-4, OV 7
  - Photographs of Studies for Decoration and Model for a Tea House for the William R. Coe Residence, circa 1900-1940 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Photographs of Studies for Decoration of the Clyde Fitch Residence, circa 1900-1940 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Photographs of Painted Decoration in the Townsend Residence, circa 1900-1940 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Photographs of Painted Decoration in Unidentified Residences, circa 1900-1940; 2 Folders (Box 2, Folder 76-77)
  - Photographs of Art Work (Portraits), circa 1900-1940 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Art Work (Female Figures), circa 1900-1940; 2 Folders (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
    Oversized material housed in Box 4, F10
  - Photographs of Art Work (The Circus and Clowns), circa 1900-1940; 2 Folders (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
  - Photographs of Art Work (Stage Performers), circa 1900-1940; 6 Folders (Box 3, Folder 6-11)
  - Photographs of Art Work (Cityscapes), circa 1900-1940; 6 Folders (Box 3, Folder 12-17)
  - Photographs of Art Work (Design for a Roadster), circa 1900-1940 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Studies for Decoration of City Hall, Trenton, New Jersey, circa 1900-1940 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Scanned with Box 2, F72
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Studies for Decoration of the William R. Coe Residence, circa 1900-1940 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Scanned with Box 2, F73
  - Oversized Photograph of a Model for a Tea House for the William R. Coe Residence, circa 1900-1940 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Art Work (Female Figures), circa 1900-1940 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Oversized Photograph of Art Work (Design for a Roadster), circa 1900-1940 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Oversized Photograph of Everett Shinn Painting the Ceiling Panel for the Henry Markle Residence, circa 1900-1940 (Box OV 7)
    Scanned with Box 2, F41
  - Oversized Photograph of Art Work (Stage Performers), circa 1900-1940 (Box OV 7)